amawebs.com 2014-11-30

# PRIVACY POLICY

                                  PRIVACY POLICY
Amawebs.com, hereafter “Amawebs.com”, is committed to implementing
measures designed to protect the privacy of those who use its Web Portal, its
Virtual offices and its services in general, (hereafter “the site” or “our site”).
Therefore, we establish rules and regulations as regards our Privacy Policy.
Matters regarding Terms and Conditions of users, advertisers, and Independent
Affiliates are included in this section.
1. THE INFORMATION WE GATHER AND HOW WE USE IT
We gather two types of information, personally identifiable information and non-
personally identifiable.
1.1 Personally identifiable information: we gather personally identifiable
information from Independent Affiliates, who willingly and fully register/sign up.
This information is related to location data such as Country, State/Province,
City, address, Postcode/Zip Code and phone numbers. As well as, Name, Last
name, Identification, email address, password to this site, and domain
personalized name –
The information we gather in our Virtual Office is for internal use exclusively.
Amawebs.com uses this information both to operate the site and for the
management of each Affiliate’s business. We may occasionally inform our
Affiliates of new features, services, promotions and products available on our
site. We do this using the information provided by our Affiliates and considering
they have accepted our terms and Conditions. We also reserve the right to
share information with our promotional partners, who provide goods and
services, if we consider our Affiliates may be interested in such.
We limit our own email regarding our services and promotions to those
registered users (Affiliates or Members) who have not “opted out” of receiving
such communications. Our solicitations clearly indicate the origin of the email
and provide the customer with a method of “opting out” of receiving future
communications of a similar nature. If the Affiliate does not wish to continue
receiving information about our features, services, promotions and products,
they must send an email with a request to legal@amarillasinternet.com.
The accuracy or veracity of the information provided by the Affiliate(s) and their
legal state are not previously verified by Amawebs.com. We consider these
factors must be truthful and show the Affiliate’s full capacity to enter an
agreement. In the case deliberately untruthful data is found, the agreement will
be terminated.
Amawebs.com reserves the right to disclose information contained within its
logs as it reasonably feels it is necessary to protect its system or business.
Specifically, but without limitation to it, the Company reserves the right to
disclose such when a user, advertiser and/or Affiliate is in violation of its Terms
of Use, Terms of Service and the Affiliation Contract or any other published
guidelines.
Furthermore, the Company reserves the right to disclose information in case a
user, advertisers and/or affiliate is involved (or reasonably suspected to be
taking part) in any kind of illegal activity. Even without subpoena, warrant or any

other kind of court order. We also reserve the right to reveal such information in
response to court and government orders, civil subpoenas, discovery requests
and as otherwise required by law. Amawebs.com cooperates with law
enforcement agencies in identifying those who may be using our servers or
services for illegal activities. Moreover, the Company reserves the right to not
only inform law enforcement agencies about any suspected illegal activity, to be
investigated or to pursue legal action; but also suspend or terminate an
agreement, Ad or any kind of membership provided an illegal activity is
suspected to be taking place.
1.2 Non-personally identifiable information: when visitors come to our site,
we may collect information indicating, among other things, which pages were
visited, the order in which they were visited and which hyperlinks were clicked.
Collecting such information involves visitor’s logging of IP addresses, operating
system, browser software, Internet Service Provider, and geographic location.
The non-personally identifiable information we gather helps us, among others
things, to monitor our internal operations, improve our services, identify the
most popular areas of our site and determine the effectiveness of our services
and promotional activities. It also helps us to improve our available online
services to assure they are high-quality and useful. We acquire this by
performing statistical analyses of the collective characteristics and behavior of
the users, and by measuring demographics and interests regarding specific
areas of our site. We provide statistical information based on this data to
advertisers, affiliates, and to current and potential promotional partners.
2. COOKIES – Tracking Cookies
A “cookie” (also known as web cookie, browser cookie, HTTP cookie, and
tracking cookie) is a recourse that allows our service to identify Affiliates as
unique users. Amawebs.com sends a “cookie” to the computer on the first visit.
This allows us to serve visitors of our site better and more efficiently. Cookies
are small text files placed on a visitor’s computer’s hard drive if permitted by the
browser. Cookies, among other things, make it easier to access our sites and
services, and help us track the pages that visitors go to, determine the length of
time visitors spend at any particular are of the site and track the services
visitors choose to use. Cookies can only be read by the server that placed
them, and they are unable to read data from hard disks, execute any code,
send viruses or destroy files. For information on how and whether cookies will
be accepted by your web browser, please refer to the documentation
accompanying your browser.
3. THIRD PARTIES INFORMATION
If you decide that you would like to discontinue receiving information from
promotional partners, please contact those third parties directly and let them
know       your      decision.     Otherwise,     contact     Amawebs.com          at
legal@amarillasinternet.com and we will advise such parties that you wish to
discontinue receiving their promotional information. Nevertheless, the Company
takes no responsibility for any actions or omissions of third parties, or the way in
which they use information received either from Amawebs.com or
independently.
